// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Name the person who replaced Ozzy Osbourne as Black Sabbath's lead singer?",
        answer: "Ronnie James Dio",
        options: [
            "Ronnie James Dio",
            "Judas Priest",
            "Dokken",
            "Whitesnake"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "To consider a band as a Big Band what is the minimum number of musicians to be needed?",
        answer: "11",
        options: [
            "11",
            "21",
            "12",
            "10"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Bjork was lead singer of what Icelandic band before pursuing a solo career?",
        answer: "The Sugarcubes",
        options: [
            "Kukl",
            "The Sugarcubes",
            "Cocteau Twins",
            "The Elgar sisters"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "In an Orchestra, which is the largest brass section instrument?",
        answer: "Tuba",
        options: [
            "Trumpet",
            "Tenor",
            "French horns",
            "Tuba"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Name the singer who released the album Alf?",
        answer: "Alison Moyet",
        options: [
            "Alison Moyet",
            "Aretha Louise Franklin",
            "Michael Joseph Jackson",
            "Christopher Maurice"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Name the singer who released the album, Here, My Dear?",
        answer: "Marvin Gaye",
        options: [
            "Frankie Gaye",
            "Bruno Mars",
            "Elton John",
            "Marvin Gaye"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Puff the Magic Dragon lives in which place",
        answer: "Hanalei",
        options: [
            "Neverland",
            "Asgard",
            "Bristol",
            "Hanalei"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "A tribute to David Bowie's ex-wife was given with a song by The Rolling stones, name the song?",
        answer: "Angie",
        options: [
            "Wild Horses",
            "Gimme Shelter",
            "Angie",
            "Satisfaction"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Name the blues great who was born Ellas Otha Bates?",
        answer: "Bo Diddley",
        options: [
            "Little Richard",
            "Muddy Waters",
            "Bo Diddley",
            "Chuck Berry"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Name the band having its name after a scientist from the movie Barbarella?",
        answer: "Duran Duran",
        options: [
            "Duran Duran",
            "A Ha",
            "Nile Rodgers",
            "Tears for fears"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Name the orchestral instrument that can play high note?",
        answer: "Violin",
        options: [
            "Viola",
            "Piccolo",
            "Violin",
            "Cellos"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Name the all-time bestselling movie soundtrack?",
        answer: "The Bodyguard: Original Soundtrack Album",
        options: [
            "I have nothing",
            "My love is your love",
            "Waiting to exhale",
            "The Bodyguard: Original Soundtrack Album"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "The most played song on American radio during the 20th century was?",
        answer: "You've Lost That Loving Feeling",
        options: [
            "You've Lost That Loving Feeling",
            "Just Once in My Life",
            "Danger Zone",
            "Soul and Inspiration"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Name the musical director of the New York Philharmonic from 1958 to 1970?",
        answer: "Jaap Van zweden",
        options: [
            "Jaap Van zweden",
            "Alan Gilbert",
            "Leonard Bernstein",
            "Kurt Masur"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "The Clawhammer is a playing style associated with an instrument, what is it?",
        answer: "Banjo",
        options: [
            "Ukulele",
            "Banjo",
            "Mandolin",
            "Fiddle"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "The 2001, Grammy Award for Best New Artist was won by whom?",
        answer: "Amy Winehouse",
        options: [
            "Sam Smith",
            "Amy Winehouse",
            "Meghan Trainor",
            "Alessia Cara"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "Who recorded 'Groove is in the Heart'?",
        answer: "Deee-Lite",
        options: [
            "Q-Tip",
            "Deee-Lite",
            "Technotronic",
            "The B-52's"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "The lead singer of Evanescence is?",
        answer: "Amy Lee",
        options: [
            "Jen Majura",
            "Lzzy Hale",
            "Ben Moody",
            "Amy Lee"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Among the following, name the musical group that had the 1967 Top 10 single, 'I Think We’re Alone Now'?",
        answer: "Tommy James and the Shondells",
        options: [
            "The Rascals",
            "The Troggs",
            "Tommy James and the Shondells",
            "The Turtles"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "The musical composition “Rhapsody in Blue was written by whom?",
        answer: "George Gershwin",
        options: [
            "Leonard Bernstein",
            "Cole Porter",
            "Claude Debussy",
            "George Gershwin"
        ]
    },
];